Student Newspapers; Collection ua809
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Albany Student Press Website, 2013 February 15 - 2017 June 1; 11; 326 captures
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 1
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 1
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 1
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 8
    crawl: 265980
    start_date: 2017-02-08T13:56:27Z
    original_start_date: 2017-02-08T13:56:27Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-02-08T14:10:49Z
    end_date: 2017-02-08T14:01:11Z
    elapsed_ms: 252825
    discovered_count: 2684
    novel_count: 584
    duplicate_count: 429
    queued_count: 1671
    downloaded_count: 1013
    warc_revisit_count: 429
    total_data_in_kbs: 47871
    duplicate_bytes: 14962930
    warc_compressed_bytes: 7568839
    doc_rate: 4.01
    kb_rate: 189.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 8
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 8
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 8
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 15
    crawl: 267265
    start_date: 2017-02-15T13:56:34Z
    original_start_date: 2017-02-15T13:56:34Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-02-15T14:10:53Z
    end_date: 2017-02-15T14:01:13Z
    elapsed_ms: 248793
    discovered_count: 2712
    novel_count: 580
    duplicate_count: 426
    queued_count: 1706
    warc_revisit_count: 426
    total_data_in_kbs: 48679
    duplicate_bytes: 14840304
    warc_compressed_bytes: 7473408
    doc_rate: 4.04
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 15
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 15
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 15
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 22
    crawl: 268621
    start_date: 2017-02-22T13:56:26Z
    original_start_date: 2017-02-22T13:56:26Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-02-22T14:09:37Z
    end_date: 2017-02-22T13:59:35Z
    elapsed_ms: 176538
    discovered_count: 2692
    novel_count: 521
    queued_count: 1678
    warc_url_count: 1004
    total_data_in_kbs: 47138
    duplicate_bytes: 15824815
    warc_compressed_bytes: 9264958
    doc_rate: 5.74
    kb_rate: 267.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 22
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 22
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 February 22
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 1
    crawl: 270137
    start_date: 2017-03-01T13:56:39Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-01T13:56:39Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-01T14:09:10Z
    end_date: 2017-03-01T13:58:47Z
    elapsed_ms: 108642
    discovered_count: 3574
    novel_count: 577
    duplicate_count: 438
    queued_count: 2559
    warc_revisit_count: 418
    total_data_in_kbs: 43652
    duplicate_bytes: 15019186
    warc_compressed_bytes: 11249838
    doc_rate: 9.34
    kb_rate: 401.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 1
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 1
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 1
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 8
    crawl: 271893
    start_date: 2017-03-08T13:56:27Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-08T13:56:27Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-08T14:08:12Z
    end_date: 2017-03-08T13:58:35Z
    elapsed_ms: 123612
    discovered_count: 3638
    novel_count: 488
    duplicate_count: 532
    queued_count: 2618
    downloaded_count: 1020
    warc_revisit_count: 507
    warc_url_count: 1003
    total_data_in_kbs: 42649
    duplicate_bytes: 15602834
    warc_compressed_bytes: 8097624
    doc_rate: 8.25
    kb_rate: 345.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 8
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 8
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 8
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 15
    crawl: 273454
    start_date: 2017-03-15T13:56:43Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-15T13:56:43Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-15T14:08:47Z
    end_date: 2017-03-15T13:58:53Z
    elapsed_ms: 113033
    discovered_count: 3601
    novel_count: 486
    duplicate_count: 517
    queued_count: 2598
    warc_revisit_count: 491
    total_data_in_kbs: 47368
    duplicate_bytes: 16554938
    warc_compressed_bytes: 13503282
    doc_rate: 8.87
    kb_rate: 419.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 15
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 15
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 15
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 22
    crawl: 285573
    start_date: 2017-03-22T13:56:29Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-22T13:56:29Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-22T14:08:34Z
    end_date: 2017-03-22T13:58:36Z
    elapsed_ms: 107373
    discovered_count: 3613
    novel_count: 454
    duplicate_count: 574
    queued_count: 2585
    downloaded_count: 1028
    warc_revisit_count: 554
    warc_url_count: 1015
    total_data_in_kbs: 47411
    duplicate_bytes: 21209891
    warc_compressed_bytes: 6872144
    doc_rate: 9.57
    kb_rate: 441.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 22
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 22
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 22
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 29
    crawl: 287312
    start_date: 2017-03-29T13:56:28Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-29T13:56:28Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-29T14:08:06Z
    end_date: 2017-03-29T13:58:34Z
    elapsed_ms: 112473
    discovered_count: 3594
    novel_count: 453
    duplicate_count: 567
    queued_count: 2574
    warc_revisit_count: 545
    warc_url_count: 1010
    total_data_in_kbs: 47973
    duplicate_bytes: 20918331
    warc_compressed_bytes: 7008557
    doc_rate: 9.07
    kb_rate: 426.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 29
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 29
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 March 29
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 5
    crawl: 288715
    start_date: 2017-04-05T13:56:24Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-05T13:56:24Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-04-05T14:08:02Z
    end_date: 2017-04-05T13:58:30Z
    elapsed_ms: 107632
    discovered_count: 3544
    novel_count: 439
    duplicate_count: 573
    queued_count: 2532
    downloaded_count: 1012
    warc_revisit_count: 548
    total_data_in_kbs: 48502
    duplicate_bytes: 20938562
    warc_compressed_bytes: 7327254
    doc_rate: 9.4
    kb_rate: 450.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 5
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 5
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 5
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 12
    crawl: 290167
    start_date: 2017-04-12T13:56:39Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-12T13:56:39Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-04-12T14:08:36Z
    end_date: 2017-04-12T13:58:44Z
    elapsed_ms: 118461
    discovered_count: 3548
    novel_count: 493
    duplicate_count: 523
    warc_revisit_count: 505
    total_data_in_kbs: 46194
    duplicate_bytes: 19829340
    warc_compressed_bytes: 7010602
    doc_rate: 8.58
    kb_rate: 389.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 12
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 12
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 12
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 19
    crawl: 291745
    start_date: 2017-04-19T13:56:28Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-19T13:56:28Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-04-19T14:10:30Z
    end_date: 2017-04-19T14:00:12Z
    elapsed_ms: 197145
    discovered_count: 1921
    novel_count: 662
    queued_count: 914
    total_data_in_kbs: 51035
    duplicate_bytes: 6638795
    warc_compressed_bytes: 10242702
    doc_rate: 5.11
    kb_rate: 258.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 19
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 19
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 19
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 26
    crawl: 297215
    start_date: 2017-04-26T13:56:32Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-26T13:56:32Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-04-26T14:09:25Z
    end_date: 2017-04-26T13:59:41Z
    elapsed_ms: 177773
    discovered_count: 2613
    novel_count: 546
    duplicate_count: 480
    queued_count: 1587
    downloaded_count: 1026
    warc_revisit_count: 480
    warc_url_count: 1016
    total_data_in_kbs: 59971
    duplicate_bytes: 19586499
    warc_compressed_bytes: 14705298
    kb_rate: 337.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 26
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 26
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 April 26
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 3
    crawl: 298623
    start_date: 2017-05-03T20:46:26Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-03T13:56:31Z
    last_resumption: 2229
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-03T23:35:48Z
    end_date: 2017-05-03T22:58:12Z
    elapsed_ms: 9082808
    document_limit: 10000
    discovered_count: 11640
    novel_count: 8953
    duplicate_count: 1055
    queued_count: 1632
    downloaded_count: 10008
    download_failures: 2269
    warc_revisit_count: 1055
    warc_url_count: 9990
    total_data_in_kbs: 617859
    duplicate_bytes: 27862940
    warc_compressed_bytes: 94655486
    doc_rate: 1.1
    kb_rate: 68.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 3
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 3
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 3
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 10
    crawl: 299974
    Limit host twitter.com to 500 documents
    Limit host twimg.com to 100 documents
    start_date: 2017-05-10T13:56:27Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-10T13:56:27Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-10T14:48:40Z
    end_date: 2017-05-10T14:36:55Z
    elapsed_ms: 2398113
    document_limit: 5000
    discovered_count: 6615
    novel_count: 3977
    duplicate_count: 1023
    queued_count: 1615
    downloaded_count: 5000
    warc_revisit_count: 1023
    warc_url_count: 4984
    total_data_in_kbs: 361974
    duplicate_bytes: 30691975
    warc_compressed_bytes: 98153145
    doc_rate: 2.08
    kb_rate: 150.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 10
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 10
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 10
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 11
    crawl: 300269
    start_date: 2017-05-11T13:56:36Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-11T13:56:36Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-14T19:29:59Z
    end_date: 2017-05-14T19:12:17Z
    elapsed_ms: 259209782
    discovered_count: 158196
    novel_count: 129680
    duplicate_count: 21136
    queued_count: 7380
    downloaded_count: 150816
    download_failures: 528
    warc_revisit_count: 21136
    warc_url_count: 150787
    total_data_in_kbs: 9152412
    duplicate_bytes: 1269641866
    warc_compressed_bytes: 810078174
    kb_rate: 35.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 11
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 11
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 11
  - Albany Student Press UAlbanys independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 17
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 18
    crawl: 301674
    Block host accounts.google.com
    start_date: 2017-05-18T13:56:33Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-18T13:56:33Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-21T14:10:08Z
    end_date: 2017-05-21T13:57:16Z
    elapsed_ms: 259210718
    discovered_count: 117824
    novel_count: 66238
    duplicate_count: 47978
    queued_count: 3608
    downloaded_count: 114216
    download_failures: 940
    warc_revisit_count: 47949
    warc_url_count: 114187
    total_data_in_kbs: 3697477
    duplicate_bytes: 2363062475
    warc_compressed_bytes: 862753616
    doc_rate: 0.44
    kb_rate: 14.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 18
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 18
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 18
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 25
    crawl: 303101
    start_date: 2017-05-25T13:56:39Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-25T13:56:39Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-27T22:17:52Z
    end_date: 2017-05-27T21:59:43Z
    elapsed_ms: 201775035
    discovered_count: 132114
    novel_count: 75397
    duplicate_count: 56717
    downloaded_count: 132114
    download_failures: 1273
    warc_revisit_count: 56716
    warc_url_count: 132087
    total_data_in_kbs: 4735276
    duplicate_bytes: 2972204490
    warc_compressed_bytes: 856693606
    doc_rate: 0.65
    kb_rate: 23.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 25
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 25
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 May 25
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 June 1
    crawl: 304306
    start_date: 2017-06-01T13:56:34Z
    original_start_date: 2017-06-01T13:56:34Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-06-03T16:04:52Z
    end_date: 2017-06-03T15:51:53Z
    elapsed_ms: 179669650
    discovered_count: 123390
    novel_count: 62424
    duplicate_count: 60966
    downloaded_count: 123390
    download_failures: 1575
    warc_revisit_count: 60966
    warc_url_count: 123363
    total_data_in_kbs: 4086366
    duplicate_bytes: 3278106680
    warc_compressed_bytes: 413854915
    kb_rate: 22.0
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 June 1
  - Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 June 1
  - WARC file for Albany Student Press – UAlbany's independent student-run newspaper, 2017 June 1